Ô£à MongoDB conectado exitosamente
Found 91 menu items
Skipping external URL for Frutas: will migrate separately
Skipping external URL for Camarones al Ajillo: will migrate separately
Skipping external URL for Filete de Pescado: will migrate separately
Skipping external URL for Coco al Horno: will migrate separately
Skipping external URL for Majarete: will migrate separately
Repair finished
ÔÜá´©Å MongoDB desconectado
Connection closed
